Guide to the Josiah K. Lilly Correspondence, 1931-1944 CAM.JKLCorr.2016
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Pittsburgh, University of (G.S. Rupp), 1940 (Box 25, Folder 891)
- Pittsburgh, University of, Press, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 892)
  Correspondence with the University of Pittsburgh Press
- Pittsburgh, University of (John G. Bowman), 1940 (Box 25, Folder 893)
- Pittsburgh, University of (Fitzgerald, R.H.), 1940 (Box 25, Folder 894)
  Correspondence with Rufus Fitzgerald from the University of Pittsburgh
- Pittsburgh, University of (Inter-office Communications), 1940 (Box 25, Folder 895)
  Correspondence with Louise Hauser; Brooks N. Sipes; Henry W. Koropal; Henry W. Koropal; Laura Mulkearn; Fletcher Hodges
- Pittsburgh, University of (John Weber), 1940 (Box 25, Folder 896)
- Q, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 897)
  Correspondence with Vivian Hope Queen; Catherine Quigley; John E. Quinn; Mary A. Quinn
- R-RILL, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 898)
  Correspondence with Radcliffe College; Ellen Radar; Bud Rainy; J. Farley Ragland; Henri E. Ragot; Hettie Rayburn Ramsey; Barbara Randall; Helen C. Randall; Mary Range; Helen Rankin; Einer Rasmussen; G.F. Rassweiler; Harold Rathbun; Enoch Rauh; Richrd S. Rauh; J.A. Rauterkus; Emma F. Ray; Edward A. Raymond; Harry H. Raymond; Lois Reardon; Myrtle Reardon; Helen L. Rearick; C.G. Reasonen; Marjorie Reddeck; Van Reddick Jr.; Peggy Redding; Martha Redmond; Sequoia Union High School, Redwood City, California; Bessie Whitmel Reed; Iva H. Reed; Marshall Foster Reed; Mary Reed; Nora T. Reed; Raymond R. Reed; C.E. Reedy; Bessie Hess Ruger; Clara Reeves; Harry Payne Reeves; Bessie Hess Reger; Gertrude E. Reid; Dorothy Reid; Eilizabeth Reid; Elizabeth Reid; Gertrude E. Reid; J.M. Reid; Marion B. Rein; Fritz Reiner; C. REimer; Milton Reinert; Thomasiana M. Reisa; Remington Rand Inc.; Thelma L. Reniff; Elizabeth Renner; Betty Jane Reno; Agnes Repplier; Alma Reuser; Douglas Wolcott Reynolds; John Hugh Reynolds; Reymoldsburgh Public Schools; Richard Rhodes; Cale Young Rice; Dean J. Rice; Edith Rice; Francis L. Rice; Mary Rice; Alderic Riehard; Alderic Richard; Donna Richards; Earl E. Richards; George D. Richards; Harry T. Richards; Bilby Richardson; Helen L. Richardson; Mattie S. Richardson; Warren Richardson; Longfellow Junior High School, Richmond California; Richmond Public Schools; Marjorie A. Rickey; W.M. Rider; Ridgefield Public Schools; Charles W. Ridinger; Betty Rigg; J.D. Riggan; Emmie D. Riggins; Edgar C. Riley; Irene Riley; Martha Riley; Paul and Thomas Riley
- RIM-ROSE (A.D.), 1940 (Box 25, Folder 899)
  Correspondence with Genevieve Ringbloom; Florence Cornwell; Evelyn B. Rittenhouse; Ella May River; Leon Robbin; Martha B. Robbins; Henry Robert, Jr.; Colleen Roberts; Lamar Roberts; Teddy Roberts; W.G. Roberts; A.W. Robertson; Clara Robertson; Herman L. Robertson; Janet Robertson; Margaret Robertson; May Robetson; William Robertson; Laura E. Robillard; Daniel Maurice Robins; Fred E. Groff; Robinson Township Schools; Francis Robinspon; George M. Robinson Jr.; Helen Robinson; Louise Robinson; W.S. Robinson; Phillip Rochlin; Abby A. Rockefeller; Abby A. Rockefeller; George Roe; William Rogan; Joyce Roger; Bettie Rogers; Edith Rogers; Harold Rogness; Walter A. Rohrbach; Gertrude Martin Rohrer; Viola T. Roling; Thomas Andrew Romeo; R.B. Romine; Teckla Ronda; Eleanor Roosevelt; Daniel C. Roper; Daniel C. Roper; Rose Marie; Jessie W. Rose; Alexander Dallas Rose
- Rose (D.C.) - RZ, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 900)
  Correspondence with Dallas Clayland Rose; Florence Rose; Kenneth Rose; Mary Rose; Parker Rose; Pearl Rose; S. Rose; Stephen Collins Foster Rose; Viola Rose; M. Roseanne; H.R. Rosen; Patsy Rosen; Sam L. Rosenbaum; Homer Rosenberger; Jennie K. Rosenberger; Claude H. Rosenberry; M. Claude Rosenberry; Ruth Rosener; A. Rosenkoff; Daniel J. Rosetty; Alia J. Ross; Hazel Ross; Marcelle Ross; Margaret P. Ross; Joseph Rossback; Gladys Jolley Rosser; Marjorie F. Rossiter; Helen C. Roth; Otto Rothert; E.H. Rothrocks; Joyce Rothrock; Karl E. Rothrock; Dirk Rotty; Joanne Roush; Florence Rousseau; Alvin S. Round; Mabel Round; J.V. Rowley; A.M. Rubert; C.C. Rudd; Junior Ruddel; John E. Rudolph; Rudy Bros. Co.; Theodore Ruel, Jr.; Carl Ruff; Lorin S. Ruff; E.S. Ruffin, Jr.; Mae A. Ruhe; Lucien V. Rule; Jean Rumry; Paul Runge; Dallmeyer Russell; Nan D. Russell; Janet Russo; Alexander G. Ruthven; Helen Rutka; John M. Rutledge; James High Ryan; James Hugh Ryan; F.I. Rypins
- Republic Bank Note Co., 1940 (Box 25, Folder 901)
  Receipts, contents of the Stephen Foster song book (folder 1 of 2)
- Republic Bank Note Co., 1940 (Box 25, Folder 902)
  Receipts, contents of the Stephen Foster song book (folder 2 of 2)
- S-SCO, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 903)
  Correspondence with Florence R. Sabin; Sacramento City School Department; Sacred Heart Academy; Sacred Heart School; Ray Saint-Amand; University Library, St. Andrews, Scotland; St. Charles School; St. Christopher's School; St. Mary's School; Pluma B. Batten; Frances Salmon; Free Library of Salt Lake City, Utah; Blanche W. Salter; Harriet Salzman; Velma Sampson; Anita Sams; Public Library of San Francisco; Jessica Fredricks; Ned Sandel; A.B. Sanderson Jr.; Horace Sandiford; K.J. Sandler; Sandler's Pharmacy; Oma Sandstrom; Lydia Santillainez; Maybelle E. Saphore; John F. Sappington; Mabel P. Sargent; Mary Sarich; David Sarnoff; Margaret Saunders; Shirley Saunders; W.A. Saunders; Lillian Saunders; Eleanor Sauville; Myrtle Savidge; Thorndike Saville; James Sawders; Henry L. Sawyers; Jonathan Sax. James H. Saylor; A.M. Seaife; Mary Scanlon; Browning Scanlon; Frances Scarborough; Charles J. Haden; Elliott Scorborough; Le Roi Scarlett; A.W. Schaefer; Frederick Schaefer; Margaret Schaeffer; Marie Schaper; H.J. Schapper; Beatrice Schapper; Beatrice Schapper; Newton Schellinger; E. Schenk; Hotel Schenley; S.L. Benedite; Sam Schiller; G. Schirmer of Louisiana, Inc.; Brunnhilde Schmitt; Eleanor T. Schmidt; Ethel M. Schneider; Joan Schneider; Vivian Schneider; Ruth B. Schnittground; Ruth B. Schnittgrund; J. Engelbert Schober; Lucille Schoener; Walter H. Schoenweis; Garnet Scholl; Lester W. Schott; Lee E. Schrecengost; G. R. Schreiber; A. S. Schrickengost; Paul Schroeder; Viola Schrolucke; Viola Schrolucke; Beatrice Schue; Hugo Schueren; Betty Schuleen; Lorenz G. Schumm; Natalie Schutzman; josephine Schwarz; Albert Charles Schweizer; Emily A. Scott; Eunice Scott; Loraine C. Scott; Margaret M. Scott; William Scott
- SEP-SHO, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 904)
  Correspondence with Cornelius D. Scully; Lena Searing; Thomas Sears; Thora Hinshaw Seaton; Henry D. Sedgwick; Marcia Sedwick; Edwin See; J.B. Seed; H.N. Seeger; Mary K. Seeley; Storrs Henry Seeley; Jay W. Seffens; I.S. Seidman; E. Seifert; John Allen Selby; Charles O. Sellman; John B. Semple; Ella Sengenberger; Mary Ella Seusing; mary Ellen Sensing; Frank B. Sessa; Catherine D. Sessions; Ruth Setzer; G.A. Severance; G.A. Severance; Elma Sexton; L.J. Sexton; William Sexton; Seymour Library; Robert J. Shckleton; Ruby Shackelford; Mary Shafer; Myrtle Shane; James F. Shankweiler; marie E. Shamkweiler; George Sharpe; Eliott Shapiro; Harry Shave; Albert Shaw; Barbara Shaw; Mary Shaw; L.P. Shawen; Joseph M. Sheeman; Minnie M. Sheffer; Frances T. Sheidy; Charles W. Shell; Hewell Shelton; B.L. Shepherd; Barbara Sheppard; G.J. Sheppard; Morris Sheppard; Sherman Clay and Co.; Betty Ann Shick; Violette Shimmin; Carol Shipman; Martha Shipman; Elise R. Shirey; Audrey Shoemaker; John A. Shoemaker; Mable Shopshire; Margaret Sholf; John Short; University; Raymond H. Shove
- SHR-SMITH (L), 1940 (Box 25, Folder 905)
  Correspondence with Gordon Shrader; Samuel W. Shroder; Robert Shrager; W.H. Shrawder; Barbara Shreves; Samuel W. Shroder; Georgia E. Shropshire; Alta Shultz; Marie Shumate; Carol E. Shuster; Shute Memorial Library; Suzanne Sickler; M. Sidora; Regis Sieffert; Ruth Sielaff; Esther Sielaff; Harlan Siffond; Margaret Sigafoose; Sophie Sigela; Sigma Alpha Tota; Mary Sikes; Violet Silhanek; Violet Silhanek; Kenneth C.M. Sills; Doris Simmonds; harry Simmonds; E. Englett Simmons; Urseile Simons; William D. Simpson; Kenneth Singer; C.A. Singleton; C.A. Singleton; Hart V. Singleton; Arthur B. Siviter; Arthur B. Siviter; Frederick W. Skiff; Constance Slattery; Yvonne Jones Slover; Hermina Smetak; Arthur W. Smith; Asestiella Reynolds Smith; Barbara Smith; C.D. Smith; Jeanne Smith; Carman B. Smith; Carleton S. Smith; Dorothy Smith; Earl Hobson smith; Edward Grandison Smith; Estelle S. Smith; F.E. Smith; Francis; Francis Edgar; George M. Smith; L.R. Smith; Leora Smith
- SMITH-(M) SPRIN, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 906)
- SPRI-STONE, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 907)
  Correspondence with C. Springer; W.F. Stacker; A. Stackman; Leigh Stadelman; Bernice Stagg; Helen Stahl; A. Stainforth; Edna Stallings; Montagress Stallings; Nellie Stanford; Roy Stanley; Roy Standridge; Ida G. Stark; State Journal Company; Helen L. Stearn; Addie Steele; Steffen; Leo Stein; Joan Steinbach; John Steinbach; Catherine Steiner; Donald Steinfirst; M. Stephanie; R.G. Stephens; Emma Stephenson; Grace Stephens; Emily Stewart; H.J. Stewart; Irene Stewart; Lorraine Stewart; Mary Stewart; Paul P. Still; Paul P. Still; Bernice Stimmel; Elenor Stimmel; Henry L. Stimson; Henry L. Stimson; Opal Stine; Iris Stith; Maybelle Stith; Harmon Stitt; Raymond Sable; Maude E. Stober; Thomas J. Stocker, Jr.; James Stokley; Leopold Stokowski; Bernard Stone; Billy Stone; Carrie P. Stone; Charles H. Stone; Harry Stone; Malcolm N. Stone; Harry Stone
- Stone-Sz, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 908)
  Correspondence with Mary Edith Stoneburner; M. Elizabeth Stong; John Storm; A.B. Stough; Johnny Jones Stough; Harriet S. Stout; M. Laurence Stout; Harriet Strader; The Strandway Book Shop; E. Wheeler; Philip G. Straus; Dorothy Bell Strawder; Wright Streeter; R.H. Stricker; Mary Strickland; W.E. Strickler; George T. Strickling; George F. Strickling; Ethalrida B. Stroh; Loilla Stroud; Walter Stroud; Mary Y. Stroup; R.A. Stroup; Buddy Struble; Marian Struble; Ray Stuart; Alma Stubblefield; M.F. Suarez; Julia K. Succop; C. Sudbeck; Ambrose Leo Suhrie; Dorothy E. Sulzbacher; Elmer G. Sulzer; William Sulzer; Herbert J. Harper; Rene Sumersille; Ruth Summly; Clayton F. Summy; Sun Telegraph; Susquehanna University Library; Louis I. Sussman; Mary C. Sutton; Swainton School; Benjamin F. Swalin; Julia A. Swanburg; C.L. Swank; J. Nell Swanzy; P.E. Swartzwelder; The Library of Swarthmore College; Angela Sweeney; Forest H. Sweet; bethel D. Swint; J.A. Sydenstricker; M. Sylvanus; Sylvia Szerkuas
- T-THO, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 909)
  Correspondence with Doris Tackitt; Tacoma School District; Bertha L. Taecker; Elois Taffe; Joseph Edwin Tague; Margaret N. Talbot; Talma Tanner; Agnes L. Tanner; Thalia J. Tarrant; Virginia Tate; Herbert Taubman; A.R. Taylor; Albert A. Taylor; Archibald Wellington Taylor; Gatha Wood Taylor; Grace Crockett Taylor; Norman B. Taylor; O.B. Taylor; Pearl H. Taylor; Paul R. Temple; Walter Teninga; State of Tennessee, department of Education; Vivian Teodori; Kathryn Terry; Henry C. Tesbitt; Anna Tesh; Texas Federation of Music Clubs; Texas State College for Women; Mary C. Theisen; Norma E. Theisen; L.E. Thiess; C.S. Thomas; Elizabeth Thomas; John B. Thomas; Rachel Thomas; Wesley Thomas; Thompson's Flower and Thrift Shop; Blanche T. Thompson; Clarence Thompson; Dorothy Thompson; Florence W. Thompson; Grace Thompson; M.A. Thompson; Helen E. Thompson; M.A. Thompson; Romules Thompson; Sarah L. Thompson; William Redd Thompson; E.L. Thomssen; R.E. Thornhill; Alexander F. Thornton; George Crossman Thornton; George C. Thornton; William T. Thornton; William F. Thornton; Margaret Thorp; Mildred Thorpe
- THP-TZ, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 910)
  Correspondence with Robert Thrane; C.T. Thrift; Martha James Thrift; Ballard Thruston; Lawrence Tibbett; M.L. Tickle; Grace Tilley; Edith W. Tillis; O.H. Tilson; Doris Evelyn Tinsley; W.C. Titus; C. Stuart Tobin; F.L. Todd; Frank L. Todd; Ida Kleber Todd; Mary Davis Todd; Hall Todd; James Tomlinson; Clara C. Tongersee; George O. Torgersen; Marie S. Totten; Betty Tower; Susan S. Towles; Charlotte Townsend; Isabel Townsend; June Tracas; June Tracas; Glen Tracy; Mary Travaglini; George H. Treadwell; Billie Treat; J.R. Treat; J.C. Trees; Katherine M. Treyens; Betty Tribble; E. Ione Trice; Buford Lewis Trimble; Grace W. Trimble; Library of Trinity College; Trinity Court Studios; E.R. Triplett; Douglas Stanley Trowbridge; Charles Troxell; Carroll Trudeau; George Tubbesing; Frederick Tupper; Juanita Tucker; Juanita S. Tucker; L.B. Tucker; Ruth B. Tucker; Margarite Tuckwiller; Tucson Music Co.; Frederick Tupper; Talmadge L. Turner; Terry Turner; W.M. Turney; Doris Tuttle; Grace M. Tuttle; Edwin P. Kilroe; Twentieth Century-Fox Film Corporation; Elizabeth Palmer Tyler; J.J. Tyler; James J. Tyler; Mabel Tyre; Nancy Lee Tyson
- Townsend, John Wilson, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 911)
- U, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 912)
  Correspondence with Adah M. Uhlman; M. Kramer; Edward A. Henry; Orah M. Upton; William Treat Upton; Lillian Urbeital; Marian L. Urland
- V, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 913)
  Correspondence with M. Valeria; Rudy Vallee; Valparaiso University; Van Buren Point Post Office; Leo Van Conant; Alta L. Van Horn; Skinner Coffee House; Susan Van Riper; Edith Van Syckle; A.W. Vance; Palmer Vance; Raymond Vance; Edna Vanderhoof; Gary Vanosdule; S.F. Varick; Robert H. Vaughan; Esther Vehrs; Agnes Velus; M. Veronica; Genevieve Vessey; Raoul George Vidas; C.L. Vincent; George E. Voncent; Norma G. Vincent; W.O. Vincent; University of Virginia; Nina M. Visscher; Elsie Vitarelle; Vera Vogel; Volkweins Music Co.; Volkwein Bros.; James H. Voorhees; Lillie Pierce Voss
- W-WAT, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 914)
  Correspondence with Helen Wachlin; Eva J. Wade; Jos. S. Wade; Joseph S. Wade; Rosalie Wade; Alice Wagersmith; Wagner's; Helen A. Waite; Florence L. Waldron; Annie Walker; Mae Walker; Ova Bee Walker; George Barclay Wallace; Henry Wallace; Nova H. Wallace; Anna R. Walling; Earll C. Waller; Jean Wallace; Mary Ambrose Walsh; W.T. Walsh; Edw. J. Walt and Sons, Inc.; Francis E. Walter; Mary L. Walters; Raymond Walters; Gibson Walters; Khadra C. Ward; Ernest H. Ward; James Ward; Joan Wardell; Hazel Warden; Dorothy Ware; Charles Warren; Charles Bradley Warren; Louis A. Warren; District of Columbia Public Library, Washington D.C.; Citizens Free Library, Washington PA; Memorial Library of Washington and Jefferson College; Carnegie Library, Washington and Lee University; Washington Stamp Exchange; H.B. Wassell; Harry Wassell; J.E. Waters; Alfred Wathen Jr.; The Foster Assembly; A.S. Wathen; Thomas C. Watkins; Earl Watson; Ellen M. Watson; June Watson; Philip Watson; Thomas J. Watson; Virginia Watson; Billy Wattenschaidt; George W. Watts; Nellie H. Watts
- WAU-WHITL, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 915)
  Correspondence with Clara Waugh; Beulah Way; Lillian Malone; Susan S. Weart; Susan Stout Weart; Helen Weaver; Martin E. Weaver; W.D. Webb; Lucile S. Webster; C.D. Webster; Conley Webster; Edward Webster; Fred H. Webster; Joan Webster; Martha Webster; Carloline Webster Weddington; Betty Weed; Wegelin; E.R. Weidlein; J.A. Weiger; Fred P. Weihl; Richie Weikel; Ray Weimer; Rita B. Weiner; Ernest T. Weir; Frank A. Weiss; Harry Weiss; Sylvia Weitz; Matthew Wiley Welch; Frances Weller; James Wellard; Wellington City Council; Deloris Wesche; Beverly Wessel; Agnes A West; Gladys West; Bertha Westbrook; Harry G. Westerfield; The University of Western Ontario; Western Pennsylvania School; Western Pennsylvania School for the Blind; The Western Reserve Historical Society; Westfield Public Schools; Golden Weston; Golden Westen; Ruby Westwood; George H. Wettach; Clara Wetteroth; Arthur Wetzler; Morrison Weyant; Laura Weyant; Alma Weyer; Rhea Weyhe; Florence Whalen; Olive Wharton; Eldon C. Wheeler; Harold Wheeler; H.R. Wheeler; Lou Wheless; Emma Lewis Whitaker; Allen White; Amelia White; Charles A. White; Ohn White; Joseph White; Lucille White; William Allen White; Mildred Whitehead; Thelma Whitehurst; E.T. Whiter; Gladys Whitesell; William O. Whiford; C.E.H. Whitlock; Everett Hale Whitlock
- WHITN-WZ, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 916)
  Correspondence with Mary Cooley Whitman; T. Carl Whitmer; C. Richard Whittemore; Who's Who in the East; Hugo Wichert; Mary Jo Wigginton; Lillian A. Wikoff; Howard G. Wilbert; Emilie Wilcox; Irene Wilde; Fred Wildnauer; Alma A. Wiley; Anne Lee Wilfong; Richard Wilhelm; Wilkinsburg High School; Wilkinsburg Gazette; Wilkinsburg School District; John R. McCune; Thomas Moore; Wilkinsburg Rotary Club; Wilkinsburg Gazette; Louise Diltz; Alis Long; Frank Crispin; Helen F. Wilkinson; hotel Willard; H.P. Somerville; Aline Williams; Ernestine Williams; Floyd; Fountine N. Williams; George E. Williams; George P. Williams; Helen E. Williams; J.L. Williams; June M. Williams; Margaret Williams; Sam Williams; Warner Williams; W.R. Williams; Charles A. Williams; Julia S. Williford; Willis Music Company; Augusta A. Willmering; J.B. Wills; Melvin Wills; Thomas E. Willson; B.F. Wilson; Wilson Junior High School; C.R. Wilson; Chester Wilson; Estelle Wilson; Eurydice Wilson; George Wilson; Helen Wilson; Phillip J. Wilson Jr.; Samuel M. Wilson; Lena Wimberly; Henry W. Winslow; Carl A. Winsor; Joseph Winston; Lulu Gains Winston; Ellen Wise; William E. Wise; Cora Wiseman; Eva A. Wiseman; William P. Witherow; Carl Wittke; J.F. Witte; Mark H. Wodlinger; Jay Wohlgemuth; Jennette Wolf; Jeanette Wolf; Bernard Wolfe; Edward A. Wolfe; Louise Womack; Louis Wolter; Mary Venable Womble; Beatrice Wood; S.G. Wood; Violet Wood; W.A. Wood; Womans Auxiliary to the State Medical Association of Texas; W.A. Wood; Ernestine Woodell; C.H. Woodford; Ray H. Woodgeard; I. Ogden Woodruff; Ida Lee Woody; Mary E. Woolley; Bailey P. Wooton; O.I. Worcester; Willie B. Worley; Clarence E. Wright; Edith A Wright; Grace Wright; John S. Wright; M.P. Wright; Yvette Wright; Henry M. Wriston; Violet Wyman; Juliette Grace Wynn; J.W. Wynne; University of Wyoming; Mildred Wulich; Anita Wunde
- Wilson, Mary Alice, January - March, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 917)
- Wilson, Mary Alice, April - June, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 918)
- Wilson, Mary Alice, July - September, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 919)
- Wilson, Mary Alice, October - December, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 920)
- XYZ, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 921)
  Correspondence with Yale University; Donald A. Wing; Yankee Incorporated; Yankton College; Mary Yarbrough; Krana Yasnitz; Elizabeth Yohe; Jay Yohe; Yonkers Museum of Science and Arts; Rowland W. York; Irene Yorke; Young Men's Christian Association of Pittsburgh; Blanche Young; Karl Young; Lewis Young; Owen D. Young; C.V. Morrison; Stark Young; Wade Young; David Leroy Yount; Kathryn R. Yurecsko; Michael Zehel; Joseph Zelechivsky; Zenobia Zimmerman; Ellen Ruth Zimmerman; N. Zitinsky
- Purchase Requisitions, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 922)
- Foster Hall Collection (Schedules), 1940 (Box 25, Folder 923)
- Pittsburgh, University of, Press, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 924)
  Correspondence with the University of Pittsburgh Press.
- Pittsburgh, University of (Fitzgerald, R.F), 1941 (Box 25, Folder 925)
  Correspondence with R.H. Fitzgerald of the University of Pittsburgh
- Pittsburgh, University of (Rupp, G.S.), 1941 (Box 25, Folder 926)
- Pittsburgh, University of (Weber, John), 1941 (Box 25, Folder 927)
- A, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 928)
  Correspondence with Alice Rogers Ablett; Joseph B. Abrahams; Catherine Achord; James Ackerman; Acme Fast Freight Inc.; Edward Acru; Eleanor Adams; John Q. Adams; L.E. Adams; Louis Adams; Viers W. Adams; Alice Addair; Dick Agliozzi; Mary Agliozzi; Lucille Adkins; Margaret Agnew; E.F. Ahnert; Kathryn B. Ahrenholtz; J.E. Aiken; James Albright; Hugo C. Aldrich; Edith Alexander; Robert A. Alexander; Violet Alexander; Bertha Allard; T.H. Allard; Curtis Allcock; Mary E. Allcock; Traffic Department, Allegheny County; Alise A. Allen; Fred L. Allen; Jay Allen; Nettie C. Allen; Philip Allen; Stanley Allen; William E. Allen; W.S. Allison; Emily R. Allensworth; Marshal Alsobrooks; Robert Alsobrooks; Willard Alsobrooks; Ambassador Hotel; Florence A. Ambler; M.F. Amen; American Red Cross; American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers; AMSCO Music Publishers; Burt T. Anderson; Charles S. Anderson; Dorothy V. Anderson; Dwight Anderson; Frederic D. Anderson; Mary E. Anderson; Mona Anderson; Ruth K. Anderson; W.G. Anderson; Janet L. Andler; E.A. Andrews; Francis M. Andrews; Mary B. Andrews; Paul Andrews; Ruth Andrews; Joann Anno; Thomas Anthony; Anonymous;William Anthony; C.O. Applegren; Maude B. Appleman; Rita S. Aprea; R.C. Archibald; Seth T. Arkills; Mary Armella; D.C. Armstrong; Edna Armstrong; J.W. Arnold; James W. Arnold; Hilegard Aschmann; George T. Ashton; Harry E. Askew; Martha L. Askew; Ethel Atkinson; Evelyn Atkinson; F.C. Atkinson; The Atlantic Monthly; Attic Book Shop; I.F. Atwood; Auburndale Journal; Auburndale Public Schools; Auburne Public Library; Mapoleon Aubut; Mae Aurelius; Bernice Austin; Bernice Austen; Emma Aveyard
- B-BN, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 929)
  Correspondence with Bacon and Wieck; Herman Baggett; Francis Bagley; Maude Foster Bailey; The Baker and Taylor Co.; F.D. Baker; Jacob C. Baker; John B. Baker; Russel L. Baker; Ben Baldridge; Theodore Baltes; Ada E. Baldwin; William C. Baldwin; Hugo Balzo; Ruth Bampton; Arthur M. Bannerman; T.O. Bannister; George R. Barber; T.A. Spalding; Bardstown United States Postmaster; Bardstown Distilleries; R.O. Baker; Myrtrie Barker; A. Beverly Barksdale; Spencer W. Barlow; Clair Barnard; Edwin N.C. Barnes; J. Foster Barnes; Marie Barnes; John Barnett; Harry Bartholomew; Wade Barton; Frank H. Barnwell; Mildred T. Barnwell; Mildred Telford Barnwell; John M. Barnum; Bernice Barr; Victor A. Barraco; Arthur B. Barrows; Frank Barrows; Edith Y. Baarrus; George Bartholomew; R.W. Bashor; I.L. Basinger; Guy H. Baskerville; Joe Boswell; Dan Bates; David E. Bates; G.D. Bates; Maxine Bates; Olive R. Batson; Caroline Batten; C.R. Baughinan; Kathryn Baum; Ruth Bauman; Baumgerdner; B.J. Beach; Jean BEach; M. Bealer; John H. Beam; George Bean; Helen L. Beardsley; B.E. Beasley; Doris M. Beatty; W.C. Bechtold; Ural M. Beck; Charles L. Beckett; Sam Beckley; E.C. Beckman; Gean Beckum; Margaret H. Beeler; Beesley Music Company; Orson Beesley; Betty Jane Beitler; Leon K. Belcher; D.D. Bell; E.B. Bell; Katherine Bell; Mary Sheppard Bell; Ardnis Beller; Hotel Belvedere; Charles Bendeich; B.V. Bender; Frank Bender; Louis Luly Bennecoff; Bennett Book Studios, Inc.; Lorena Bennett; Nadine Bensley; A.T. Benson; Boyd Bentrott; Jos. Bergeim; S.S. Berger; Berlitz Translation Service; Marie Bernard; Nora Lee Bernard; A.D. Bernard; Jerome Berry; Mary Bertille; Dorothea N. Bestor; Theodosia Bettilyon; Albert Adam Bieber; Marie Bienvenu; Nola Bigger; Carl Biggers; Edward B. Birge; Birmingham Conservatory of Music; Norma Bish; Fern Bishop; John E. Bishop; LeRoy S. Bishop; W.J. Bivens; Howard T. Black; Melvin Blackard; Blackstone Studios; Emma Blair; L.N. Blair; Stuart Blake; Jeannette Blawchard; Florence E. Blankfield; Elizabeth Blankenship; Charles C. Blieffert; Melvin St. J. Blitch; Ethel S. Blizzard
- BO-BZ, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 930)